Activities and Organizations Records UA024
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Activities and Organizations Records
1870 -- 1994
1857 -- 2014
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Miller, Russell E.
UA024
12.16 Linear Feet 24 boxes and 2 oversized folders
210 Digital Object(s)
Arrangement
This collection organized in two series: Activities and Organizations; and Photographs.
Custodial History
This collection, organized by subject, was created by Russell Miller in the process of preparing his history of Tufts University, Light on the Hill.
All material accessioned prior to 1997 was originally arranged by subject, and no attempt was made to recreate original order. Material relating to administering the collection was removed to the documentation files of the collection in the archives.
Most of the newsclippings, photographs, press releases, and correspondence have been separated from the subject files. These types of materials are present however, throughout the subject files as well.
Some files have been removed by DCA staff over time and incorporated into their own collections.
Biographical / Historical
Russell Elliott Miller was a Professor of History, University Historian and Archivist of Tufts University, and author of "Light on the Hill, A History of Tufts College from 1852 to 1952" and the second volume "Light on the Hill, A History of Tufts University since 1952." He was born in Bloomington, Minnesota, on April 25, 1916, to one of the last pioneer families in the Minnesota prairie. His mother spoke Dakota Sioux, which she had learned as a child. He received a B.A. in Education in 1937 and an M.A. in political science in 1939, both from the University of Florida at Gainesville. From 1942 to 1946, he served in the Army Air Corps as an enlisted man, rising to the rank of technical sergeant. Initially with personnel and classification, he was finally assigned to the historical section (intelligence) at the headquarters of the troop carrier command. In 1948 he earned a Master of Arts in history from Princeton University and came to Tufts that same year.
In 1952 he received a PhD from Princeton, and in 1964 Tufts appointed him Professor of History and University Historian and archivist. He taught courses ranging from the history of western civilization to the history of the American frontier. In 1966, he published "Light on the Hill, A History of Tufts College from 1852 to 1952." That year he received the Distinguished Service Award from the Tufts Alumni Association and became an honorary member of Phi Beta Kappa. In 1975 he became the Walter S. Dickson Professor of English and American History and chaired the Department of History from then until 1980. He was voted Emeritus Professor of English and American History in 1981 and received an honorary Doctor of Letters degree in 1983. In 1986, he completed the second volume of Tufts history, "Light on the Hill II, A History of Tufts University since 1952."
Conditions Governing Access
Some material in this collection may be protected by copyright and other rights. Please see "Reproductions and Use" on the Digital Collections and Archives website for more information about reproductions and permission to publish. Copyright to all materials created by Tufts University employees in the course of their work is held by the Trustees of Tufts University.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains correspondence, directories, photographs, newspaper clippings, publications, minutes, budget documents, and membership lists of various Tufts student organizations. It also includes Hemispheres - a Tufts publication, as well as course evaluations up to 1991.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Student life; Student Activities -- Student Government, Clubs, and Organizations; Student Activities -- Performing Arts; Student Activities -- Athletics; Student Activities -- Student Publishing; Student activism
- Activities and organizations, 1857 -- 2019; UA024.001; 9.45 Linear Feet; 192 Digital Object(s)
  Scope and Contents
  This collection, organized by subject, was created by Russell Miller in the process of preparing his history of Tufts University, Light on the Hill. This collection contains correspondence, directories, pictures, newspaper clippings, minutes, budget documents, and membership lists of various Tufts student organizations. It also includes Hemispheres - a Tufts publication, as well as course evaluations up to 1991. Part of this collection is minimally processed and may be unavailable for research. Please contact the DCA office for more information.
  All material accessioned prior to 1997 was originally arranged by subject, and no attempt was made to recreate original order. Material relating to administering the collection was removed to the documentation files of the collection in the archives.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged alphabetically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - General, 1911 -- 1985; UA024.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Aero Club, 1910; UA024.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
    - Glider in flight, 1910; UA024.001.001.00002.00001; Munro, Melville S. (Box 1)
      Gliders (Aeronautics); Aero Club
    - Students testing glider, 1910; UA024.001.001.00002.00002; Munro, Melville S. (Box 1)
      Student activities; Students; People; Gliders (Aeronautics); Aero Club
  - African American Cultural Center, 1969 -- 1978; UA024.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Alethea, 1961 -- 1965; UA024.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
    - Althea Party, 1965; UA024.001.001.00004.00001 (Box 1)
      Student activities; Students; Clubs; People; Women; Althea Club
    - Althea Smoking Party, 1961; UA024.001.001.00004.00002 (Box 1)
    - Althea Club, 1961; UA024.001.001.00004.00003 (Box 1)
  - All Around Club, 1898 -- 1950; UA024.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Alpha Omicron Pi, 1935 -- 1964; UA024.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
    - Alpha Omicron Pi Cup, 1935; UA024.001.001.00006.00001; Munro, Melville S. (Box 1)
      Trophies; Cups; Alpha Omicron Pi
    - Alpha Omicron Pi Pins, 1935; UA024.001.001.00006.00002; Munro, Melville S. (Box 1)
      Pins; Alpha Omicron Pi
    - Alpha Omicron Pi, 1964; UA024.001.001.00006.00003 (Box 1)
      Student activities; Students; Clubs; People; Women; Alpha Omicron Pi
    - Alpha Omicron Pi, 1964; UA024.001.001.00006.00004 (Box 1)
    - Alpha Omicron Pi, 1961; UA024.001.001.00006.00005 (Box 1)
  - Alpha Epsilon Pi, 1955 -- 1965; UA024.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
    - Alpha Epsilon Pi Reception, 1962; UA024.001.001.00007.00001 (Box 1)
      Student activities; Students; Clubs; Reception; Men; Fraternities; Alpha Epsilon Pi
    - Alpha Epsilon Pi Reception, 1962; UA024.001.001.00007.00002 (Box 1)
    - Alpha Epsilon Pi, 1905 -- 1962; UA024.001.001.00007.00003 (Box 1)
      3x3
      Student activities; Students; Clubs; Men; People; Fraternities; Alpha Epsilon Pi
    - Alpha Epsilon Pi, 1965; UA024.001.001.00007.00004 (Box 1)
    - Alpha Epsilon Pi, 1965; UA024.001.001.00007.00005 (Box 1)
    - Alpha Epsilon Pi, 1965; UA024.001.001.00007.00006 (Box 1)
    - Alpha Epsilon Pi, 1961; UA024.001.001.00007.00007 (Box 1)
    - Alpha Epsilon Pi Smoking Party, 1963; UA024.001.001.00007.00008 (Box 1)
    - Alpha Epsilon Pi, 1963; UA024.001.001.00007.00009 (Box 1)
    - Alpha Epsilon Pi, 1963; UA024.001.001.00007.00010 (Box 1)
    - Alpha Epsilon Pi, 1955; UA024.001.001.00007.00011 (Box 1)
    - Alpha Epsilon Pi rush week pamphlet, 1966; UA024.000425 (Box 1)
      Immediate Source of Acquisition
      Gift of Bill Primack A'66, 2022, accession UA-2023-029.
  - Alpha Kappa Gamma, 1904 -- 1910; UA024.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Alpha Kappa Kappa, 1900; UA024.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
    This date is approximate.
  - Alpha Kappa Pi, 1937; UA024.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
    - Alpha Kappa Pi House Ground Breaking, June 12, 1937; UA024.001.001.00010.00001 (Box 1)
      Student activities; Students; Clubs; People; Fraternities; Construction; Alpha Kappa Pi
    - Alpha Kappa Pi House Ground Breaking, June 12, 1937; UA024.001.001.00010.00002 (Box 1)
    - Alpha Kappa Pi House Ground Breaking, June 12, 1937; UA024.001.001.00010.00003 (Box 1)
    - Alpha Kappa Pi House Construction, 1937; UA024.001.001.00010.00004 (Box 1)
      Student activities; Students; Clubs; Fraternities; Construction; House; Alpha Kappa Pi
    - Alpha Kappa Pi House Construction, 1937; UA024.001.001.00010.00005 (Box 1)
    - Alpha Kappa Pi House Construction, 1937; UA024.001.001.00010.00006 (Box 1)
  - Alpha Sigma Pi, 1955 -- 1969; UA024.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
    - Alpha Sigma Phi, 1958; UA024.001.001.00011.00001 (Box 1)
      Student activities; Students; Clubs; Fraternities; Reception; Alpha Sigma Phi
    - Alpha Sigma Phi House, 1960; UA024.001.001.00011.00002 (Box 1)
      Student activities; Students; Clubs; Fraternities; Houses; Alpha Sigma Phi
    - Alpha Sigma House at Professors Row, 1960; UA024.001.001.00011.00003 (Box 1)
    - Alpha Sigma Phi, 1955; UA024.001.001.00011.00004 (Box 1)
      Student activities; Students; Fraternities; People; Men; Clubs; Alpha Sigma Phi
    - Alpha Sigma Phi, 1960 -- 1969; UA024.001.001.00011.00005 (Box 1)
    - Alpha Sigma Phi, 1961; UA024.001.001.00011.00006 (Box 1)
      75 This date is approximate.
      Student activities; Students; Fraternities; Clubs; People; Men; Alpha Sigma Phi
  - Alpha Tau Omega, 1906 -- 1962; UA024.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
    - Alpha Tau Omega House, 1906; UA024.001.001.00012.00001 (Box 1)
      Student activities; Students; Clubs; Fraternities; House; Alpha Tau Omega
    - Alpha Tau Omega House interior, 1906; UA024.001.001.00012.00002 (Box 1)
      Student activities; Students; Clubs; Fraternities; House; Interior views; Alpha Tau Omega
    - Alpha Tau Omega House interior, 1906; UA024.001.001.00012.00003 (Box 1)
      Student activities; Students; Clubs; Fraternities; House; Chimneys (architectural elements); Interior views; Alpha Tau Omega
    - Alpha Tau Omega House Dining Room, 1906; UA024.001.001.00012.00004; Unknown (Box 1)
      Student activities; Students; Clubs; Fraternities; Dinners and Dining; Interior views; House; Alpha Tau Omega
    - Alpha Tau Omega House Dining Room, 1906; UA024.001.001.00012.00005 (Box 1)
    - Alpha Tau Omega GTV Dance, March 28, 1928; UA024.001.001.00012.00006 (Box 1)
      Student activities; Students; Clubs; Fraternities; Dances and Dancing; Alpha Tau Omega
    - Alpha Tau Omega House Ground Breaking, June 13, 1936; UA024.001.001.00012.00007 (Box 1)
      5.75x4
      Student activities; Students; Clubs; Fraternities; Men; House; Construction; Alpha Tau Omega
    - Alpha Tau Omega House Ground Breaking, June 13, 1936; UA024.001.001.00012.00008 (Box 1)
    - Alpha Tau Omega House Ground Breaking, June 13, 1936; UA024.001.001.00012.00009 (Box 1)
    - Alpha Tau Omega House Construction, July 22, 1936; UA024.001.001.00012.00010 (Box 1)
    - Alpha Tau Omega House Construction, February 11, 1936; UA024.001.001.00012.00011 (Box 1)
    - Alpha Tau Omega House Construction, July 22, 1936; UA024.001.001.00012.00012 (Box 1)
    - Alpha Tau Omega House Construction, February 11, 1936; UA024.001.001.00012.00013 (Box 1)
    - Alpha Tau Omega House, 1936; UA024.001.001.00012.00014 (Box 1)
      Student activities; Students; Fraternities; House; Men; Alpha Tau Omega
    - Alpha Tau Omega, February 11, 1936; UA024.001.001.00012.00015 (Box 1)
      Student activities; Students; Clubs; Men; People; Alpha Tau Omega
    - Alpha Tau Omega, March 24, 1936; UA024.001.001.00012.00016 (Box 1)
    - Alpha Tau Omega, 1936; UA024.001.001.00012.00017 (Box 1)
    - Alpha Tau Omega, 1940; UA024.001.001.00012.00018 (Box 1)
    - Alpha Tau Omega Basketball Team, 1927; UA024.001.001.00012.00019 (Box 1)
      Student activities; Students; Clubs; Fraternities; Men; Athletics; Basketball (Men's); People; Alpha Tau Omega
    - Alpha Tau Omega, 1927; UA024.001.001.00012.00020 (Box 1)
      Student activities; Students; Fraternities; Men; People; Alpha Tau Omega
    - Alpha Tau Omega, 1962; UA024.001.001.00012.00021 (Box 1)
    - The Alpha Tau Omega Signal Another Tufts Touchdown, 1962; UA024.001.001.00012.00022 (Box 1)
      Student activities; Students; Fraternities; Men; People; Athletics; Football; Alpha Tau Omega
    - Alpha Tau Omega Alumni Reception, 1962; UA024.001.001.00012.00023 (Box 1)
      Student activities; Students; Fraternities; Alumni and alumnae; Alpha Tau Omega
    - Alpha Tau Omega Alumni Reception, 1962; UA024.001.001.00012.00024 (Box 1)
    - Alpha Tau Omega, 1961; UA024.001.001.00012.00025 (Box 1)
      Student activities; Students; Fraternities; People; Men; Clubs; Alpha Tau Omega
    - Alpha Tau Omega, 1961; UA024.001.001.00012.00026 (Box 1)
    - Alpha Tau Omega, 1962; UA024.001.001.00012.00027 (Box 1)
    - Alpha Tau Omega, 1962; UA024.001.001.00012.00028 (Box 1)
    - Alpha Tau Omega, 1962; UA024.001.001.00012.00029 (Box 1)
    - Alpha Tau Omega Competition, October, 1962; UA024.001.001.00012.00030 (Box 1)
      Student activities; Students; Fraternities; Clubs; Automobiles; Alpha Tau Omega
    - Alpha Tau Omega Competition, 1907; UA024.001.001.00012.00031 (Box 1)
      Student activities; Students; Clubs; Fraternities; Graduate students; Alpha Tau Omega
  - Alpha Xi Delta, 1941; UA024.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
    - Alpha Xi Delta Sorority, 1941; UA024.001.001.00013.00001; Waid Studio (Box 1)
      Name of the studio is embossed on photo.
      Student activities; Students; Sororities; Women; Clubs; People; Fontneau, Barbara Marshall; Trednnick, Emily Otto; Alpha Xi Delta
  - Alpha Epsilon Phi, 1922; UA024.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - Alpha Omicron Pi - photographs, 1998 -- 1999; UA024.001.001.00015 (Box Small Map Case 1 Drawer 4)
    Photographs of Alpha Omicron Pi members.
  - Axon Press, 1968; UA024.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - Beta Kappa, 1925 -- 1928; UA024.001.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - Canterbury Club, 1946 -- 1949; UA024.001.002.00003 (Box 2)
    - Officers of the Canterbury Club, 1946; UA024.001.002.00003.00001; Office of Public Relations (Box 2)
      People; Students; Women; Student activities; Bunker, Carolyn E.; Dimond, Nancy; Simonds, Barbara L.; Canterbury Club
    - Canterbury Club, 1949; UA024.001.002.00003.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 2)
      People; Students; Coeducation; Student activities; Canterbury Club
  - Chapel exercises, 1883 -- 1990; UA024.001.002.00004 (Box 2)
  - Chi Omega, 1935 -- 1961; UA024.001.002.00005 (Box 2)
    - Chi Omega Bench, 1961-10; UA024.001.002.00005.00001; Unknown (Box 2)
      Benches; Student activities; Chi Omega
    - Lets go Chi O!, UA024.001.002.00005.00002; Unknown (Box 2)
      Women; Sororities; Chi Omega
    - Dime Please! Chi Omega parade float, UA024.001.002.00005.00003; Unknown (Box 2)
      "Dime Please!"
      Sororities; Student activities; Women; Parade floats; Chi Omega
    - Chi Omega Scholarship Cup, 1936; UA024.001.002.00005.00004; Unknown (Box 2)
      Trophies; Sororities; Scholarships; Chi Omega
    - Chi Omega Tennis Trophy, 1935-03-20; UA024.001.002.00005.00005; Unknown (Box 2)
      Trophies; Tennis; Sororities; Chi Omega
    - Chi Omega Tennis Trophy, 1936-03-20; UA024.001.002.00005.00006; Unknown (Box 2)
    - Chi Omega Children's Christmas at the South End House, UA024.001.002.00005.00007; Unknown (Box 2)
      Children; Christmas; Sororities; Santa Claus; Chi Omega
    - Chi Os at South End House, UA024.001.002.00005.00008; Unknown (Box 2)
    - Chi O Navels, UA024.001.002.00005.00009; Unknown (Box 2)
      Female Impersonators; Sororities; Chi Omega
    - Chi Omega Female Impersonators, UA024.001.002.00005.00010; Unknown (Box 2)
    - Chi Omega group photograph, UA024.001.002.00005.00011; Unknown (Box 2)
      Sororities; Women; Chi Omega
  - Chironian Society, 1964 -- 1968; UA024.001.002.00006 (Box 2)
  - Christian Guild, 1911; UA024.001.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - Class officers, UA024.001.002.00008 (Box 2)
  - Combined Art Series, 1962 -- 1964; UA024.001.002.00009 (Box 2)
  - Commons Club, 1908 -- 1968; UA024.001.002.00010 (Box 2)
  - Communications cluster, 1982; UA024.001.002.00011 (Box 2)
  - Commuters Association of Jackson, 1965; UA024.001.002.00012 (Box 2)
  - Concerts, 1870 -- 1944; UA024.001.002.00013 (Box 2)
  - Debating, 1975; UA024.001.002.00014 (Box 2)
    - Debating Trophy, 1975; UA024.001.002.00014.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 2)
      Student activities; Trophies; Debating Team
  - Delta Tau Delta, 1900 -- 1975; UA024.001.002.00015 (Box 2)
    - Delta Tau Delta Chapter House, 1900; UA024.001.002.00015.00001; Unknown (Box 2)
      Fraternities; Chapter houses; Delta Tau Delta
    - Delta Tau Delta house, 1975; UA024.001.002.00015.00002; Unknown (Box 2)
      Fraternities; House; Delta Tau Delta
    - Delta Tau Delta Dance Decorations, 1939-12-08; UA024.001.002.00015.00003; Unknown (Box 2)
      Fraternities; Dances; Decorations; Delta Tau Delta
    - Delta Tau Delta Dance Decorations, 1939-12-08; UA024.001.002.00015.00004; Unknown (Box 2)
      Fraternities; Dances; Decorations; Delta Epsilon
    - Delta Tau Delta Dance Decorations, 1939-12-08; UA024.001.002.00015.00005; Unknown (Box 2)
    - Delta Tau Delta Dance Decorations, 1939-12-08; UA024.001.002.00015.00006; Unknown (Box 2)
    - Delta Tau Delta Construction, 1936-07-22; UA024.001.002.00015.00007; Unknown (Box 2)
      Construction; Fraternities; Building sites; Delta Tau Delta
    - Delta Tau Delta members, 1970; UA024.001.002.00015.00008; Unknown (Box 2)
      Fraternities; Men; Delta Tau Delta
    - Delta Tau Delta Lincoln Snow Sculpture, 1970; UA024.001.002.00015.00009; Unknown (Box 2)
      "What Manner Is This Place"
      Fraternities; Sculpture; Snow; Lincoln, Abraham 1809-1865; Delta Tau Delta
    - Delta Tau Delta Banjo Player, 1970; UA024.001.002.00015.00010; Unknown (Box 2)
      Fraternities; Men; Banjo; Musicians; Delta Tau Delta
    - Delta Tau Delta Fraternity House, 1975; UA024.001.002.00015.00011; Duette Photographers (Box 2)
      Fraternities; Buildings; Delta Tau Delta
    - Delta Tau Delta Fraternity Members, 1965; UA024.001.002.00015.00012; Unknown (Box 2)
  - Delta Upsilon, 1938 -- 1939; UA024.001.002.00016 (Box 2)
    - Delta Upsilon Snow Sculpture, UA024.001.002.00016.00001; McLean Photography (Box 2)
      Fraternities; Sculpture; Snow; Delta Upsilon
    - Delta Upsilon Members at Dinner, UA024.001.002.00016.00002; Unknown (Box 2)
      "Feeding Time at the Zoo!"
      Fraternities; Dinners and Dining; Men; Delta Upsilon
    - Delta Upsilon House Construction, UA024.001.002.00016.00003; Unknown (Box 2)
      "Delta Upsilon House (new) Construction"
      Fraternities; Construction; House; Delta Upsilon
    - Delta Upsilon Snow Sculpture, UA024.001.002.00016.00004; Hayden, Robert L. (Box 2)
    - Delta Upsilon Delegates, 1939-02-11; UA024.001.002.00016.00005; Unknown (Box 2)
      "Delta Upsilon Delegates"
      Fraternities; Men; Delta Upsilon
    - Delta Upsilon Members, UA024.001.002.00016.00006; Unknown (Box 2)
    - Delta Upsilon Trophy Case, 1938-02-15; UA024.001.002.00016.00007; Munro, Melville S. (Box 2)
      "#3 Photo-Mural Goddard Chapel Tower for the Library of the new Fraternity House of Delta Upsilon, Tufts College, Mass."
      Fraternities; Trophies; Chapels; Towers (building divisions); Delta Upsilon
    - Deltal Upsilon Members, UA024.001.002.00016.00008; Unknown (Box 2)
    - Delta Upsilon Elephant Decorations, UA024.001.002.00016.00009; Duette Photographers (Box 2)
      Fraternities; Decorations; Elephants; Men; Delta Upsilon
    - Delta Upsilon Minstrel Show, UA024.001.002.00016.00010; Squitteri, Jean (Box 2)
      Anthony, Hope S. --Cleary, Lawrence T. --Borg, Victor --Dodge, Barbara H (identified on reverse of photograph)
      Fraternities; People; Student activities; Anthony, Hope S.; Cleary, Lawrence T.; Borg, Victor; Dodge, Barbara H; Delta Upsilon
    - Delta Epsilon Fraternity House, UA024.001.002.00016.00011; Unknown (Box 2)
      Fraternities; Chapter houses; Delta Upsilon
  - Delta Upsilon, 1914 -- 1936; UA024.001.002.00017 (Box 2)
    1914 Twenty-eighth Anniversary and Initiation Banquet Program; 1915 Annual Report to the Alumni; 1936 Pamphlet on a New Chapter House; Photographs
  - Delta Tau Delta, photographs, 1915 -- 1919; UA024.001.002.00018 (Box Shared 74)
  - Band, 1926 -- 1961; UA024.001.003.00001 (Box 3)
    - Band, UA024.001.003.00001.00001; Unknown (Box 3)
      Music; Instruments; Tufts University
    - Band Sing on the Rez, UA024.001.003.00001.00002; Unknown (Box 3)
    - Band, Homecoming Day, 1935-10-26; UA024.001.003.00001.00003; Unknown (Box 3)
      Music; Instruments; Football; People; Tufts University
    - Band Jamboree, 1939-10-09; UA024.001.003.00001.00004; Unknown (Box 3)
      Music; Instruments; People; Tufts University
    - Band Jamboree, 1939-10-09; UA024.001.003.00001.00005; Unknown (Box 3)
      Music; Instruments; People; Building sites; Tufts University
    - Band Jamboree, 1939-10-09; UA024.001.003.00001.00006; Unknown (Box 3)
    - Band Jamboree, 1939-10-09; UA024.001.003.00001.00007; Unknown (Box 3)
    - Band Jamboree, 1939-10-09; UA024.001.003.00001.00008; Unknown (Box 3)
      Music; Instruments; People; Building sites; Parades; Tufts University
    - Band Jamboree, 1939-10-09; UA024.001.003.00001.00009; Unknown (Box 3)
    - Tufts Band, 1926; UA024.001.003.00001.00010; Unknown (Box 3)
    - Tufts Band, 1961; UA024.001.003.00001.00011; Unknown (Box 3)
    - Tufts Band, 1929-10-12; UA024.001.003.00001.00012; Unknown (Box 3)
      Music; Instruments; People; Athletic fields; Building sites; Flags; Tufts University
    - Tufts Band, UA024.001.003.00001.00013; Unknown (Box 3)
    - Tufts Band, UA024.001.003.00001.00014; Unknown (Box 3)
      Music; Instruments; People; Trees; Tufts University
    - Marching Band, 1938-04-13; UA024.001.003.00001.00015; Unknown (Box 3)
      Music; Instruments; People; Trees; Building sites; Athletic fields; Tufts University
    - Marching Band, Homecoming Day, 1936-11-07; UA024.001.003.00001.00016; Unknown (Box 3)
    - Band Jamboree, 1939-10-09; UA024.001.003.00001.00017; Unknown (Box 3)
      People; Trees; Building sites; Women; Tufts University
    - Laurence White, 1936-04-28; UA024.001.003.00001.00018; Unknown (Box 3)
      People; Men; White, Laurence
    - Marching Band, UA024.001.003.00001.00019; Unknown (Box 3)
      People; Athletic fields; Instruments; Music; Building sites
    - Band, UA024.001.003.00001.00020; Unknown (Box 3)
      People; Instruments; Music
    - Band, UA024.001.003.00001.00021; Unknown (Box 3)
      People; Instruments; Music; Food service
    - Band on Cousens Gym Steps, 1935-01-19; UA024.001.003.00001.00023; Unknown (Box 3)
      People; Instruments; Music; Building sites
    - Band, 1932-11-17; UA024.001.003.00001.00024; Unknown (Box 3)
    - Tufts College Band, 1929-12-02; UA024.001.003.00001.00025; Unknown (Box 3)
    - Tufts Marching Band, UA024.001.003.00001.00026; Unknown (Box 3)
      People; Instruments; Music; Building sites; Elephants
    - Tufts College Band, UA024.001.003.00001.00027; Unknown (Box 3)
    - Tufts Band, UA024.001.003.00001.00028; Unknown (Box 3)
      People; Instruments; Music; Athletic fields
    - Tufts Band, UA024.001.003.00001.00029; Unknown (Box 3)
    - Band Concert, 1945-07-27; UA024.001.003.00001.00030; Unknown (Box 3)
      People; Instruments; Music; Building sites; Trees
    - Tufts College Band, UA024.001.003.00001.00031; Blandford Studio (Box 3)
      People; Building sites
    - Summer School Band, UA024.001.003.00001.00032; Unknown (Box 3)
      People; Building sites; Music; Instruments
    - Poverty Parade, 1939; UA024.001.003.00001.00033; Unknown (Box 3)
      People; Building sites; Music; Instruments; Trees; Signs; Parades
    - Marching Band, UA024.001.003.00001.00034; Unknown (Box 3)
      People; Building sites; Music; Instruments; Trees; Signs; Athletic fields
    - Marching Band, UA024.001.003.00001.00035; Unknown (Box 3)